{
"response_code": 0,
"results": [
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Which%20company%20did%20Gabe%20Newell%20work%20at%20before%20founding%20Valve%20Corporation%3F",
"correct_answer": "Microsoft",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Apple",
"Google",
"Yahoo"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20a%20type%20of%20monster%20found%20in%20Minecraft%3F",
"correct_answer": "Skeleton",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Werewolf",
"Vampire",
"Minotaur"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "In%20Kingdom%20Hearts%2C%20how%20many%20members%20does%20Organization%20XIII%20have%20in%20total%3F",
"correct_answer": "14",
"incorrect_answers": [
"10",
"13",
"12"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20title%20of%20song%20on%20the%20main%20menu%20in%20Halo%3F",
"correct_answer": "Halo",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Opening%20Suite",
"Shadows",
"Suite%20Autumn"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20a%20Humongous%20Entertainment%20game%20franchise%3F",
"correct_answer": "Commander%20Keen",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Pajama%20Sam",
"Putt-Putt",
"Freddi%20Fish"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Who%20is%20the%20leader%20of%20Team%20Instinct%20in%20Pok%C3%A9mon%20Go%3F",
"correct_answer": "Spark",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Candela",
"Blanche",
"Willow"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20NOT%20a%20summon%20in%20the%20game%20%22South%20Park%3A%20The%20Stick%20of%20Truth%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Towelie",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jesus",
"Mr.%20Hankey",
"Mr.%20Slave"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "Aperture%20Science%20CEO%20Cave%20Johnson%20is%20voiced%20by%20which%20American%20actor%3F",
"correct_answer": "J.K.%20Simmons",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nolan%20North",
"John%20Patrick%20Lowrie",
"Christopher%20Lloyd"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "What%20were%20the%20first%20two%20blocks%20in%20%22Minecraft%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Grass%20and%20Cobblestone",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Grass%20and%20Stone",
"Crafting%20Table%20and%20Cobblestone",
"Cobblestone%20and%20Stone"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "easy",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20last%20name%20of%20the%20primary%20female%20protagonist%20of%20Final%20Fantasy%20VIII%3F",
"correct_answer": "Heartilly",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Loire",
"Almasy",
"Trepe"
]
}
]
}